HEY.
HI.
SORRY I'M LATE.
DID I MISS ANYTHING?
WELL, JOEY STUFFING
15 OREOS IN HIS MOUTH.
FIFTEEN?
YOUR PERSONAL BEST. YEAH.
( muffled ):
MM-MM.
SO, WHERE WERE YOU?
OH, ON A DATE.
I MET THIS GIRL
ON THE TRAIN
GOING TO A
MUSEUM UPSTATE.
OH, YEAH, HOW'D
YOU MEET HER?
WHICH MUSEUM?
NO. ANSWER HIS.
OKAY, IT WAS JUST ME AND HER
AT THE BACK OF THE TRAIN
AND I SAT NEAR THE DOOR
SO SHE'D HAVE TO PASS BY ME
IF SHE WANTED TO, LIKE,
SWITCH CARS.
SHE WAS TOTALLY AT MY MERCY.
WERE YOU SO LATE BECAUSE YOU
WERE BURYING THIS WOMAN?
NO, I'M GETTING BACK NOW
BECAUSE SHE LIVES
IN POUGHKEEPSIE.
SHE SEEMS REALLY GREAT
BUT SHE'S, LIKE, TWO
AND A HALF HOURS AWAY.
HOW CAN SHE BE GREAT IF
SHE'S FROM POUGHKEEPSIE?
'KAY, THAT JOKE
WOULD'VE KILLED IN ALBANY.
DONE.
I DID IT.
HUH. WHO'S STUPID NOW, HUH?
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY, THEY'RE LIGHTING
THE BIG CHRISTMAS TREE TONIGHT.
UM, THAT PAPER'S
TWO WEEKS OLD.
ALL RIGHT, WHO KEEPS LEAVING
OLD NEWSPAPERS IN THE TRASH?
I REALLY WANTED
TO TAKE KATHY TO THIS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I MISSED IT.
HEY, YOU KNOW, AT LEAST
YOU HAVE SOMEBODY TO
MISS THAT STUFF WITH.
I HATE BEING ALONE
THIS TIME OF YEAR.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
IT'LL BE VALENTINE'S DAY
THEN MY BIRTHDAY,
THEN BANG--
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
THEY'RE LIGHTING
THAT DAMN TREE AGAIN.
OH, I WANT SOMEBODY.
YOU KNOW? I WANT A MAN.
I MEAN
IT DOESN'T EVEN HAVE TO
BE A BIG RELATIONSHIP.
YOU KNOW, JUST A FLING
WOULD BE GREAT.
REALLY? I DIDN'T THINK GIRLS
EVER JUST WANTED A FLING.
WELL, LET ME TELL
YOU SOMETHING.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE I'VE BEEN FLUNG.
WELL, I KNOW WHAT I'M GIVING YOU
FOR CHRISTMAS.
THERE ARE SOME NICE GUYS
AT MY OFFICE.
YOU WANT ME TO SET YOU UP?
YEAH. WAIT A MINUTE.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
THAT I'VE BEEN SINGLE.
HOW COME YOU'VE NEVER
OFFERED THIS BEFORE?
WELL, I HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
I'M... I'M HAPPY.
SO, I NO LONGER FEEL THE NEED
TO GO OUT OF MY WAY
TO STOP OTHERS
FROM BEING HAPPY.
OKAY.
BUT NO ACCOUNTANTS.
OH, AND NO ONE
FROM, LIKE, "LEGAL."
I DON'T LIKE GUYS
WITH BORING JOBS.
OH, AND ROSS WAS LIKE, WHAT,
A LION TAMER?
HEY!
HEY.
WHAT'S WRONG, MON?
EVERYBODY AT
THE RESTAURANT
STILL HATES ME.
I THOUGHT I WAS
MAKING HEADWAY.
EVERYONE
WAS SMILING AT ME ALL DAY
AND THEN I'D GET OFF WORK
AND FIND OUT
THAT THEY WROTE THIS...
ON MY CHEF'S HAT.
HEY, MAYBE THEY MEANT TO WRITE
"QUIET, BITCH."
HEY, HONEY,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
FINE, JUST TRYING TO BE NICE.
I HAVE NOT BEEN PICKED ON
THIS MUCH
SINCE I WAS IN KINDERGARTEN
AND THEY HAD TO BRING IN SOMEONE
FROM JUNIOR HIGH
TO DO THE SEESAW WITH ME.
( laughing )
AW.
THEY'RE DOING EVERYTHING
THEY CAN TO MAKE ME QUIT.
IF IT WERE ANY OTHER JOB,
I WOULD
BUT THIS IS SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR
MY WHOLE LIFE.
WELL, HONEY,
YOU'RE THE BOSS.
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST YELL AT THEM?
OR FIRE THEM?
I WOULD LOVE TO, BUT I CAN'T.
YOU KNOW I'M NOT GOOD
AT CONFRONTATION.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU COULD DO?
I REMEMBER READING
ABOUT THIS DIRECTOR--
I THINK IT WAS ORSON WELLES--
WHO AT THE BEGINNING OF A MOVIE
WOULD HIRE SOMEBODY
JUST SO HE COULD FIRE THEM
IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
THEN THEY WOULD ALL KNOW
WHO WAS BOSS.
HEY, MON,
I'M NOT DOING ANYTHING.
WHY DON'T YOU
FIRE ME?
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
DO YOU KNOW HOW TO WAITER?
GOOD ENOUGH TO GET FIRED.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE HIRED.
HEY.
OH.
THAT MUST BE WHY I GOT FIRED
LAST WEEK.
DOES THIS ORSON WELLES GUY
DIRECT BURGER KING COMMERCIALS?
YES.
I SAY, DREW
ARE YOU SEEING ANYBODY
RIGHT NOW?
UH, UH, I'M NOT ASKING FOR ME.
UH...
I'M, I'M NOT, I'M NOT GAY.
I'M NOT ASKING YOU OUT.
I-I-I'M NOT GAY.
I DIDN'T THINK YOU WERE GAY.
I DO NOW.
SEE, MY FRIEND,
MY FRIEND, RACHEL
SHE WANTS TO BE SET UP.
AH. I JUST GOT OUT
OF A BIG RELATIONSHIP.
I'M NOT LOOKING
FOR ANYTHING SERIOUS.
OH, WELL, YOU KNOW
THAT MIGHT BE OKAY.
EVEN IF IT WAS
JUST KIND OF A FLING
THAT MIGHT BE ALL RIGHT
WITH RACHEL.
WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA.
IS THIS "HOT RACHEL
THAT YOU TOOK
TO THE CHRISTMAS PARTY"
RACHEL?
OH, BY THE WAY,
THAT IS HER FULL NAME.
OH, WOW.
I'M FREE FOR HER.
WAIT A SECOND.
I DIDN'T SAY
I WASN'T FREE.
WHY DON'T WE
TALK THIS OVER
AT THE RANGER GAME
TOMORROW?
HOLD ON.
YOU KNOW, I JUST GOT
A BOX OF CUBANS.
MAYBE I BRING 'EM
BY YOUR OFFICE
AROUND, UH, 5:00?
WELL, THAT'S
A LITTLE LATER
THAN I, UH,
GENERALLY CARE TO STAY
BUT SURE.
MAYBE BEFORE
THE GAME
WE CAN ENJOY SOME EIGHT-YEAR-OLD
SMALL BATCH BASIL HAYDENS.
WELL, I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT THAT IS, BUT LET'S!
HEY, YOU GUYS, I'M WRITING
A HOLIDAY SONG FOR EVERYONE.
DO YOU WANT TO HEAR IT?
YEAH.
YES.
OKAY.
( clearing throat )
♪ HAPPY HANUKKAH, MONICA ♪
♪ MAY YOUR CHRISTMAS BE SNOWY,
JOEY ♪
♪ HAPPY NEW YEAR,
CHANDLER AND ROSS ♪
♪ SPIN THE DREIDEL, RACHEL. ♪
PHEEBS, IT'S GREAT.
OH, YAY.
BUT YOU KNOW, UH
"RACHEL" DOESN'T RHYME
WITH "DREIDEL."
I KNOW, BUT IT'S SO HARD.
NOTHING RHYMES
WITH YOUR STUPID NAME.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
LOTS OF THINGS
RHYME WITH RACHEL.
BAGEL, MALE, JAIL,
BAIL, CABLE
MAYPOLE...
ALL GOOD. THANKS.
DO YOU MAYBE
HAVE A NICKNAME
THAT'S EASIER TO RHYME?
DIDN'T YOUR DAD
USED TO CALL
YOU "PUMPKIN?"
OH, YEAH.
PUMPKIN? YEAH?
BUT DID HE EVER CALL YOU, LIKE,
"BOODOLPH?"
HELLO, CHILDREN.
( all greeting Chandler )
HAVE I GOT
THE 50 GUYS FOR YOU!
REALLY?
I SHOWED THEM
THIS PICTURE OF YOU
AND GUYS
WERE BUYING ME DRINKS
GIVING ME STUFF.
KNICKS TONIGHT?
SURE.
WHERE ARE THE SEATS?
WHEREVER. I'VE GOT, LIKE, 20.
SO, WILL I LIKE
ANY OF THESE GUYS?
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO, UH...
I'M GOING TO PLAY THE FIELD
JUST A LITTLE BIT MORE.
CHANDLER...
GUYS ARE SIGNING OVER
THEIR 401(k)s TO ME.
YOU WORK WITH ROBOTS?
YES.
OKAY, THERE IS
THIS ONE GUY, PATRICK.
HE'S REALLY NICE,
HE'S FUNNY, HE'S A SWIMMER.
OH, I LIKE SWIMMERS' BODIES.
AND HIS FATHER
INVENTED THAT MAGNETIC STRIP
ON CREDIT CARDS.
OH! I LIKE CREDIT CARDS.
SEE? NOT BAD
AT THIS "FIXING UP" THING, HUH?
SO, WHAT DOES HE DO?
HE WORKS IN
THE FINE FOODS DIVISION.
YOUR COMPANY HAS A
FINE FOODS DIVISION?
IT'S A BIG COMPANY.
I... IF YOU...
NOW, WAIT A SECOND.
YOU MAKE FOOD AND ROBOTS?
NO.
NO, THE ROBOTS
JUST WORK FOR THEM.
ALL RIGHT,
I'M GOING TO GO TO WORK.
DOES ANYBODY HAVE
A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
YEAH, LADY, I DO.
I GOT
A PROBLEM WITH THAT.
YOU WANT A PROBLEM?
I'LL GIVE YOU A PROBLEM.
OH, WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO, FIRE ME?
YOU BET YOUR ASS
I'M GOING TO FIRE YOU.
SEE YOU LATER.
THANKS.
OH, WOW, I
SHOULD GET GOING.
I'VE GOT A
DATE TONIGHT.
OH, YEAH?
WITH WHO?
YOU KNOW THAT GIRL
WHO LIVES IN POUGHKEEPSIE?
YEAH.
NOT HER.
YEAH, THIS IS SOMEONE ELSE I MET
AND I-I CAN'T DECIDE
BETWEEN THE TWO OF THEM.
YOU KNOW,
THE ONE FROM POUGHKEEPSIE
EVEN THOUGH
SHE'S A TWO-HOUR TRAIN RIDE AWAY
IS REALLY PRETTY, REALLY SMART,
AND A LOT OF FUN
BUT THIS OTHER GIRL...
WELL, SHE LIVES RIGHT UPTOWN.
WELL, SHE'S...
WELL, SHE'S, SHE'S
JUST AS PRETTY.
I GUESS SHE'S SMART.
SHE'S NOT FUN.
IF SHE'S NO FUN
WHY DO YOU WANT
TO DATE HER AT ALL?
WELL, I WANT TO GIVE HER
ANOTHER CHANCE, YOU KNOW?
SHE LIVES SO CLOSE.
AND, AT THE END OF THE DATE
THE OTHER TIME
SHE SAID SOMETHING THAT WAS--
IF SHE WAS KIDDING--
WAS VERY FUNNY.
ON THE OTHER HAND
IF SHE WASN'T KIDDING,
SHE'S NOT FUN, SHE'S STUPID
AND KIND OF A RACIST.
HEY.
HEY, MAN.
OOH, HOW WAS YOUR FIRST DAY
WORKING AT THE RESTAURANT?
DAMN!
HEY.
OH, WHAT HAPPENED TO
YOUR FANCY CHEF JACKET?
THEY BAKED IT.
I CAN'T TAKE THIS
ANYMORE.
I'M GOING
TO CALL A MEETING.
I'M GOING TO FIRE YOU
TONIGHT.
YOU GOT IT.
OH, OH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE STILL A TINY
BIT ON FIRE THERE.
OH, THANKS.
LISTEN, I THINK YOU GOT IT.
OH, CHANDLER!
YOU HAVE THE BEST
TASTE IN MEN.
WELL, LIKE FATHER, LIKE SON.
PATRICK AND I HAD SUCH
A GREAT TIME LAST NIGHT.
I MEAN, I THINK THIS
COULD TURN INTO
SOMETHING SERIOUS.
REALLY? I THOUGHT
YOU WEREN'T EVEN LOOKING
FOR SOMETHING SERIOUS.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE LOOKING
FOR SOME KIND OF A FLING.
WELL, YOU KNOW, POSSIBLY.
YOU DIDN'T... TELL HIM
THAT, THOUGH... RIGHT?
W'UH...
NO?
YOU TOLD THIS GUY THAT I
WAS LOOKING FOR A FLING?!
YOU DON'T TELL THE GUY THAT!
I'D BE THRILLED
IF I HEARD
THAT SOME HOT GIRL
WAS JUST LOOKING TO GET...
OH, I SEE.
OH! BETWEEN YOU TELLING HIM
I WANTED TO HAVE A FLING
AND ME PUTTING OUT
ON THE FIRST DATE
OH, HE'S SO GOING TO
GET THE WRONG IDEA!
JOEY, COULD YOU PASS
THE CHEESE?
YEAH. LISTEN,
I'D PREFER IT
IF YOU WOULDN'T
CALL ME JOEY.
SINCE I DON'T
KNOW ANYONE HERE
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE FUN
TO TRY OUT A COOL
WORK NICKNAME.
HEY, DRAGON.
HERE'S YOUR TIPS FROM
MONDAY AND TUESDAY.
OH. LOOKS LIKE THERE'S, LIKE,
300 BUCKS IN THIS ONE.
YEAH, PEOPLE GET
PRETTY GENEROUS
AROUND THE HOLIDAYS.
AND IT NEVER HURTS TO
WEAR TIGHT TROUSERS.
OKAY.
WOULD THE WAITERS
GATHER 'ROUND
TO HEAR
TONIGHT'S SPECIALS?
FIRST, THERE'S
A CHILEAN SEA BASS
PREPARED WITH A MANGO RELISH
ON A BED...
WHY IS NOBODY
WRITING THESE DOWN?
BECAUSE WE CAN
REMEMBER THEM.
AND BECAUSE YOU'RE ALL GOING
TO MAKE UP FAKE SPECIALS
AND MAKE ME COOK THEM
LIKE YOU DID
THE OTHER NIGHT?
WELL, SURE, THAT, TOO.
OKAY. FORGET THE SPECIALS
FOR A MINUTE.
UM, ALL RIGHT,
HERE'S THE THING.
FOR THE LAST TWO WEEKS,
I HAVE, UH...
TRIED REALLY HARD TO CREATE
A POSITIVE ATMOSPHERE.
CAN'T HEAR YOU.
A POSITIVE
ATMOSPHERE...
BUT I-I'VE HAD IT UP TO HERE.
FROM NOW ON,
IT IS GOING TO BE MY WAY...
OR THE HIGHWAY, ALL RIGHT?
DOES ANYBODY
HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
HEY, NEW GUY?
I SAID...
DOES ANYBODY HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH THAT?
NO, MA'AM.
HEY, HE HAS A NAME.
IT'S DRAGON.
YOU WANT TO KNOW
YOUR NAME?
CHECK YOUR HAT.
WE DID THE HAT, RIGHT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
I AM SO SORRY.
I WAS GOING
TO DO IT. REALLY.
BUT THEN I WAS
STANDING THERE
WITH $327 IN ONE HAND
AND $238
IN THE OTHER HAND
AND I WAS THINKING, "WOW.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE I HAD..."
327 PLUS $238.
JOEY, WE HAD A DEAL.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HERE.
I'VE GOT TO FIRE YOU.
AND I'VE GOT TO PAY RENT.
( sighs )
LOOK
HOW ABOUT THIS?
YOU DON'T FIRE ME.
INSTEAD, I STAY HERE,
I GAIN THEIR TRUST
AND THEY'LL START LISTENING
TO ALL THE NICE THINGS
I'VE BEEN SAYING ABOUT YOU.
WHAT KIND OF THINGS
YOU BEEN SAYING?
NOTHING YET.
THEY REALLY HATE YOU
AND I WANT TO FIT IN.
♪ HAPPY, HAPPY HANUKKAH ♪
♪ CHANDLER AND MONICA ♪
♪ MERRY, MERRY... ♪
OOH, YOU KNOW...
YOU KNOW WHAT, PHEEBS?
I'M NOT JEWISH, SO...
SO ROSS DOESN'T REALLY
DECORATE HIS TREE WITH FLOSS
BUT YOU DON'T HEAR HIM
COMPLAINING, DO YOU? GOD!
( yells out )
WHAT?
BAD DREAM?
I WASN'T SLEEPING.
OH, YEAH?
THEN WHAT WAS
PHOEBE'S SONG ABOUT?
THE ONE WITH THE CAT.
I GOT TO GO.
I GOT ANOTHER DATE.
OH, SO DID YOU
PICK ONE YET?
NO.
IT TURNS OUT THE ONE FROM UPTOWN
WAS MAKING A JOKE
BUT IT WAS A DIFFERENT JOKE
THAN I THOUGHT.
IT WASN'T THAT FUNNY.
SO I'M STILL TORN.
YOU DON'T REALLY LIKE
THE ONE UPTOWN
AND YOU'RE TOO EXHAUSTED FROM
DATING THE ONE IN POUGHKEEPSIE
SO I SAY YOU END THEM BOTH.
TAKE A TRAIN UP TO POUGHKEEPSIE
AND YOU BREAK UP WITH HER
AND ON YOUR WAY BACK,
YOU BREAK UP WITH UPTOWN
AND THEN BY THE TIME
YOU GET HOME TONIGHT
YOU'RE DONE.
YOU KNOW WHAT, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
YEAH. I HAD A SIMILAR PROBLEM
WHEN I LIVED IN PRAGUE.
PRAGUE?
SO MUCH YOU DON'T KNOW.
( slams )
( thuds )
CHANDLER
PATRICK JUST ENDED
THINGS WITH ME.
DID YOU OR DID YOU
NOT TELL HIM
THAT I WAS LOOKING FOR
A SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP?
I DID! I ABSOLUTELY DID!
YOU IDIOT!
I'M SURE YOU'RE RIGHT,
BUT WHY?
YOU DON'T TELL A GUY
THAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
A SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP.
YOU DON'T TELL
THE GUY THAT!
NOW YOU SCARED HIM AWAY.
OH, MAN.
I AM SORRY.
I AM SO, SO SORRY.
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD NEVER
BE ALLOWED TO TALK TO PEOPLE.
I KNOW! I KNOW!
NOW I'M RIGHT BACK
WHERE I STARTED.
OH, THIS SUCKS.
BEING ALONE SUCKS!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE GOING TO MEET SOMEBODY.
YOU'RE
A GREAT CATCH.
WHEN I WAS TELLING
ALL THOSE GUYS ABOUT YOU
I DIDN'T HAVE TO LIE ONCE.
REALLY?
YEAH.
YOU GRADUATED
MAGNA CUM LAUDE, RIGHT?
NO.
AW, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I GOT TWO TICKETS
TO TONIGHT'S RANGER GAME.
YOU WANT
TO COME WITH ME?
CUTE GUYS
IN LITTLE SHORTS?
SURE.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
IT'S A HOCKEY TEAM
SO IT'S ANGRY CANADIANS
WITH NO TEETH.
WELL, THAT SOUNDS FUN, TOO.
THANK YOU.
OKAY.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN
WITH A WOMAN?
WHAT?
CHANDLER, WHAT IS
THE MATTER WITH YOU?
SO THERE IS NO GOOD TIME
TO ASK THAT QUESTION.
THE STATION IS POUGHKEEPSIE.
POUGHKEEPSIE.
ROSS?
WAKE UP.
ROS... ROSS!
ROSS! ROSS!
I NEED MORE SWORDFISH.
CAN YOU GET ME
SOME MORE SWORDFISH?
I DON'T SPEAK ENGLISH.
YOU DID A MINUTE AGO.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO TELL YA.
FINE.
OKAY, VERY FUNNY.
( banging ):
CAN SOMEBODY
LET ME OUT, PLEASE?
COME ON, I'M COLD!
( clattering pans )
AND COVERED
IN MARINARA SAUCE!
( banging ):
COME ON, LET ME OUT!
YOU FOUND THAT HANDLE,
DID YA?
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
WELL, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I'M A GOOD PERSON
AND I'M A GOOD CHEF
AND I DON'T DESERVE TO HAVE
MARINARA SAUCE ALL OVER ME.
IF YOU WANT ME
TO QUIT THIS BAD
ALL YOU HAVE TO...
HEY! CHEF GELLER.
YOU KNOW THAT LITTLE SPEECH
YOU MADE THE OTHER DAY?
WELL, I GOT A PROBLEM WITH IT.
YOU DO?
YOU BET I DO.
I JUST, UH...
WASN'T LISTENING THEN,
IS ALL.
WELL, IF YOU WANT A PROBLEM
I'LL GIVE YOU A PROBLEM.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO,
FIRE ME?
YOU BET YOUR ASS
I'M GOING TO FIRE YOU.
NOW, GET OUT OF MY KITCHEN!
GET OUT!
ALL RIGHT
ANYBODY ELSE
GOT A PROBLEM?
HOW ABOUT YOU, CHUCKLES?
YOU THINK THIS IS FUNNY NOW?
NO.
HOW ABOUT IF DANCE AROUND
ALL COVERED IN SAUCE, HUH?
YOU THINK IT'S FUNNY NOW?
NO. IT'S REALLY GOOD.
GOOD.
NOW, TAKE THOSE SALADS
TO TABLE FOUR
AND YOU,
GET THE SWORDFISH
AND YOU--
GET A HAIRCUT.
LAST STOP, MONTREAL.
THE STOP IS MONTREAL.
WHAT?
I MADE A BET WITH MYSELF
THAT YOU HAD BEAUTIFUL EYES.
NOW THAT I SEE THEM, I WIN.
WHAT?
WE'RE AT MY STOP
BUT WOULD YOU LIKE
TO HAVE COFFEE?
ARE WE REALLY IN MONTREAL?
YES, WE ARE.
SO, COFFEE?
COFFEE SOUNDS GREAT.
WAIT. SO, YOU LIVE
IN MONTREAL?
NO, BUT IT'S JUST A TWO-HOUR
FERRY RIDE TO NOVA SCOTIA.
( loudly ):
WELL, I SHOULD HAVE THOUGHT
ABOUT MY WIFE AND KIDS
BEFORE I TALKED BACK
TO CHEF GELLER.
( quietly ):
THANKS.
YEP, LOOKS LIKE IT'S GOING
TO BE A LEAN CHRISTMAS
AT THE DRAGON HOUSE
THIS YEAR.
ENOUGH.
LEAN, LEAN, LEAN.
♪ WENT TO THE STORE,
SAT ON SANTA'S LAP ♪
♪ ASKED HIM TO BRING MY FRIENDS
ALL KINDS OF CRAP ♪
♪ HE SAID ALL YOU NEED
IS TO WRITE THEM A SONG ♪
♪ THEY HAVEN'T HEARD IT YET
SO DON'T TRY TO SING ALONG ♪
♪ NO, DON'T SING ALONG ♪
♪ MONICA, MONICA ♪
♪ HAVE A HAPPY HANUKKAH ♪
♪ SAW SANTA CLAUS ♪
♪ HE SAID HELLO TO ROSS ♪
( strumming )
♪ AND PLEASE TELL JOEY ♪
♪ CHRISTMAS WILL BE SNOWY... ♪
♪ AND RACHEL AND CHANDLER ♪
♪ HAS A...( mumbles ) HANDLER. ♪
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]